say this is the best, worst logo of all time, the cone?
Yeah, by far, right?
The logo of VLC is so iconic, right?
Like, we are a team with a small number of people,
and the icon is known everywhere.
I go to middle of nowhere in India or in China.
People know the cone, right?
And 25% of the website traffic that
comes to our main website is cone player, right?
So many people don't know VLC, right?
They know the cone player.
There's something that Google Forrest, cone player.
They go on Google, and they put cone player,
and they download VLC, right?
So that's iconic.
And once we tried to change it as a joke, right?
We said it was going to be a type of caterpillar
construction, and we said that during April 1st.
We had around 10,000 emails saying, no,
don't change the logo and so on.